The events of this movie are not canon. We are in an alternative universe either set around the time of episode 63 or 73.
Don't watch this movie before episode 76.
Tianwu Sect Mountain Village
Not so fast !
Be careful.
Ah Hua
Villager
This person has been sitting here for 4 months...
Isn't he hungry ?
You know what,
he might be an Immortal.
Hmph
Immortals live above the clouds.
I think
he's just a lunatic.
You little brats...
I looked for you everywhere !
The Village Chief !
We're coming !
Quickly come back,
the Immortals will arrive soon.
We're here.
Always running around,
you never give me a moment of peace !
Ah Hua !
On my way !
My daughter,
Village Chief
do your best.
If you get selected into the Immortal sect,
you'll become an Immortal too !
Immortal...
Greetings, Immortal...
Tianwu Sect disciple
The Tianwu Sect has no grudge against you,
why are you trying to kill us all ?!
Our Eternal Night Devil City has taken control of the Sea of Devils.
We know everything and can do anything.
A minor sect like yours that dares to defy orders
deserves to become nourishment for our expansion !
Formation !
Protect the mortals !
Break !
Get those tasty mortals.
My daughter...
I hope you will live a good life.
Father !
Who are you !?
Wang Lin's avatar
Early stage Soul Formation
Thank you, Immortal !
Thank you !
He really is an Immortal...
Thank you for saving us.
What strange poison is this ?
This man won't last long.
Wan'er !
Renegade Immortal
Battle of the Gods
Subtitles by Bonobosubs https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
50 years ago,
Producer
Sun Huaizhong
the ancient fog that covered the Sea of Devils
evaporated overnight.
Lead Executive Producer
Ma Yankun
General Planning
Cui Chao
This plunged the Sea of Devils into endless war.
Executive Producers
Feng Yi
Zhou Wang
Executive Producers
Zhang Jianing
Wang Junchao
Producer
Yan Lihua
Amidst the chaos,
Eternal Night Devil City
suddenly emerged
Marketing Coordinators
Wu Shuang
Liu Yazheng
Operations Coordinators
Lu Shaofang
Qin Dongyan
Shuang Li
Xing Zhidong
by unifying the inner and outer seas.
But all of this
Literary Coordinator
Niu Shipu
Screenwriters
Wang Ziyue
Liu Mengwei
Head Screenwriter
Ma Hua
was just the beginning for the Eternal Night Devil City.
Massive plundering and slaughter
Co-director
Ma Hua
Executive director
Shi Xiong
has left the surrounding rank 3 cultivation countries
in great danger.
Directorial team
Zhao Wenbo    Lin Junyue
Zhao Yong       Que Wei
Du Wenkai       Zu Xinlong
Executive Producer
Liu Zhu
Zhang Shipei
Directors
Li Zhenfeng
Wang Jianxin
3 days ago
War God Shrine
Burning Fire Alliance
Lin Tao
War God Shrine disciple
This...
is our War God Shrine's treasure.
The Divine Path.
Wen Kuang
Envoy of the Eternal Night Devil City
Peak Late stage Nascent Soul
It can greatly increase the probability of forming a Nascent Soul.
Forming a Nascent Soul ?
Are you insulting me ?
No !
You promised to kill me,
I beg you...
After offending the envoy,
do you think you can just die ?
Wait !
I...
I know where the remnants of the War God Shrine are.
Divination Cups
And...
I know the other sect treasures of the Burning Fire Alliance !
I beg you !
There's the country of Xuanwu
and the country of Chu !
Chu's Cloud Sky Sect
has grade 5 alchemists !
The Cloud Sky Sect ?
Cloud Sky Sect
Country of Chu
Surrender your Soul Blood immediately.
Submit your entire sect to me.
Only then can the Cloud Sky Sect can have a place
Li Muwan
Cloud Sky Sect Leader
Late stage Core Formation
in Eternal Night Devil City.
The Cloud Sky Sect has stood for thousands of years.
We've never made enemies.
But if anyone threatens the Cloud Sky Sect,
we will definitely fight back !
Junior,
Yun Tianzi
Elder of the Cloud Sky Sect
Late stage Nascent Soul
don't bring trouble upon yourself.
Formation !
Yes !
Kill !
The thunder breaks the clouds,
the sky becomes your cage !
Sect Protection Formation...
Activate !
Interesting...
Peak Late stage Nascent Soul ?
You fool
dared to be insolent !
A Soul Formation artifact ?!
Senior Yun Tianzi,
come back !
You overestimated yourself...
Go !
Look out !
What is that ?
Everyone, be careful !
Be careful !
Something's wrong...
Is this...
poisonous rain ?
Within 7 days,
your Sect Leader may find me at Poison Devil City
to pledge allegiance.
Otherwise, in 7 days, the poison will activate.
Which would be a real shame.
Who are you ?
What do you really want !?
You are the greatest opportunity of Eternal Night Devil City...
By the way,
my name is
Wen Kuang.
It doesn't work...
Try other pills.
Try sealing your meridians.
Junior Brother,
wake up, Junior Brother !
This poison is strange
it cannot be expelled with cultivation.
The past 3 days,
I've tried every pill in the sect
and none of them can neutralize
this poison.
If it spreads to the neck,
we'll all probably...
Elders,
Wan'er promised to protect everyone.
But I need time.
We will find the antidote.
Sect Leader,
the antidote
must be with that envoy.
Shouldn't we submit
to save our lives ?
This is also
for the Cloud Sky Sect's sake...
Sect Leader,
please consider the Cloud Sky Sect.
Scram !
Senior !
You're back...
Don't worry,
I'll handle everything.
Senior...
Did everything work out ?
Soul Formation cultivation ?
The poison has been suppressed !
Ancestor !
That Wen Kuang
is at Poison Devil City in inner Sea of Devils,
he must have the antidote.
It seems I didn't kill enough people
in the Sea of Devils.
Come,
let's do some killing.
But...
The Sea of Devils is different now...
Then we'll kill our way through again.
We've reached the outer Sea of Devils.
Spirit Beast Trench
Inner Sea of Devils
Poison Devil City is very close.
The inner Sea of Devils
looks nothing like the outer sea.
After the fog disappeared,
a strange black rain fell
which caused mutations in the local fauna and flora.
Wan'er's poison
is getting harder to suppress.
I need to quickly investigate this Poison Devil City.
Senior, look !
This is a Luo Lin fruit !
Careful !
So beautiful...
Wan'er...
I'm fine.
Follow me.
Poison Devil City
Inner Sea of Devils
Dusi Shangren
Poison Devil City Lord
Early stage Soul Formation
Greetings Envoy !
Welcome Envoy.
Old servant Dusi
welcomes the envoy of Eternal Night Devil City.
Poison Devil City
is honored of your presence.
This old servant spared no effort
in finding this precious top-quality spirit stone
as a gift for you.
This trash
is unworthy of me.
This old servant deserves death,
I beg Envoy for forgiveness.
Poison Devil City rewards everyone.
Here are your contribution tokens.
Thank you Master !
Senior,
isn't the Sea of Devils
supposed to be a lawless area ?
I never expected
that the inner sea could be so orderly.
Bastard !
Don't you dare steal the loot !
A bunch of evil cultivators
sharing the loot equally ?
They even punish thieves together...
This thief...
doesn't he look familiar ?
Shangguan Mo
Wang Lin's disciple (self-proclaimed)
Late stage Core Formation
Shangguan Mo
Master's wife ?!
Mas...
Master ?
You're Master !
I've missed you both so much !
Do you know Poison Devil City ?
Of course !
It's where devil cultivators fight to enter.
I've heard
that even the envoy from Eternal Night Devil City,
Lord Wen Kuang,
has been visiting the city recently !
Wen Kuang...
Wan'er,
let's go check that place
and take what we need.
That envoy Wen Kuang you mentioned,
where is he now ?
The envoy always rests
at the Poison Devil City Lord's cave.
Judging by the time,
he should be there.
Wildfire Team is recruiting !
It's even more orderly here
than in rank 4 countries outside the sea.
There must be
overwhelmingly powerful experts behind this.
This is the doing of the Poison Devil City Lord.
The Poison Cultivation Pills he developed
can rapidly increase the power of Core Formation cultivators.
I came here
hoping to get one.
But these pills
require contribution tokens.
Tokens are obtained by participating in city operations.
This is how the City Lord
controls nearly a third of the Sea of Devils' cultivators.
Is Poison Devil City
the Eternal Night Devil City ?
Not at all.
Poison Devil City ? No way !
It's merely one of the 7 cities
controlled by the Eternal Night Devil City.
Eternal Night Devil City...
Legend says its City Lord,
is the Lord of Eternal Night.
No one has ever seen him,
yet he controls
the entire Sea of Devils.
Master...
May I ask Envoy to convey this to your Master.
This old servant
would like to hear the teachings of the Lord of Eternal Night.
If the Lord approves,
I will summon you.
Thank you, Envoy.
This old servant will take his leave.
Eternal Night never fades !
Master,
disciple apologizes for interrupting your seclusion.
I have made significant gains over this trip.
I followed your instructions
and while sweeping the Burning Fire Alliance,
I discovered a great opportunity for us !
Wen Kuang...
Do you know that
to achieve Eternal Night's grand plan,
your master has watched the Land of the Ancient God day and night
for thousands of years...
Disciple also works for Eternal Night's grand plan !
For thousands of years,
countless people have entered the Land of the Ancient God.
Including many Soul Formation experts.
Yet only one truly acquired its treasures.
A single person
named Wang Lin...
I've never heard of this person.
A name ?
An honorary title ?
He needs no such things.
His actions
are his title.
His past
is littered with corpses
piled up into mountains.
And each time he enters the Sea of Devils,
it brings calamity.
He holds heaven defying artifacts,
is a Soul Devourer,
cleared the Hundred-Day Execution Order by killing thousands.
He is the Land of the Ancient God's sole survivor.
He triggered a tribulation
which evaporated the fog of the sea.
And you
dared to attack the sect under his protection
and you even poisoned his cultivation partner !?
Wen Kuang...
Didn't I teach you
that opportunity also means calamity ?
Your life belongs to Eternal Night.
Return to the city at once.
So you're Wen Kuang...
Hand over the antidote !
Dusi,
kill him.
This is your chance to join Eternal Night Devil City.
Finally, this old servant gets to prove his loyalty.
Attack !
Senior, be careful !
Green Poison Sword
Poison Domain...
Activate !
Poison Domain
So this is a domain ?
Don't worry about it.
Accept your death !
This youth's domain is astonishing !
Dusi,
what are you waiting for ?
You arrogant brat !
Don't think you can stop me from meeting the Lord of Eternal Night !
Human
Gu
Note: A gu is a type of parasite.
Art !
Die !
Is this what you call a calamity ?!
Before me, Wen Kuang,
you will only find death !
How...
How can this be ?
Impossible !
The Human Gu Art was created by Senior Brother Meng Qingfan !
How could some Early stage Soul Formation cultivator break it !?
I have some experience with poison.
Do you know
who is responsible
for the death of Hunchback Meng ?
You're...
Wang Lin !?
To die by your hand
means I have no regrets in this life...
Trash !
It's your turn now.
Hand over the antidote !
Explode !
Wan'er !
Senior...
Master Wang Lin...
Did you refine this poison ?
I'm truly ashamed,
this old servant merely assisted the Lord of Eternal Night in refining it.
I know little about it...
As the Poison Devil City Lord,
you have studied poison all your life.
Can you neutralize this poison ?
This old servant is deeply sorry.
This poison...
I've studied it long,
but I cannot understand it.
It must have many hidden layers.
As far as I know,
even Wen Kuang doesn't have its formula or antidote.
To cure it,
you must go to Eternal Night Devil City.
Eternal Night Devil City...
Eternal Night Devil City
Inner Sea of Devils
Here is Wen Kuang's Soul Blood jade !
Even if Wen Kuang is talented
for reaching peak Late stage Nascent Soul in 100 years,
he always causes trouble !
How could he inherit the title of City Lord ?
Well,
the Lord must have his reasons.
There is no need to discuss his decisions.
Enter the Ancestral Hall,
worship the Ancestors !
Wen Kuang
Lord of Eternal Night
Late stage Soul Formation
It's been 6 000 years since the Eternal Night Country's defeat
that forced us to retread into the Sea of Devils.
I've been waiting for an opportunity
to breakthrough to Soul Transformation
in order to charge out of the Sea of Devils
and reclaim the Eternal Night's rightful place !
But now, things are getting complicated...
This is too sudden,
I need more time to prepare.
Junior Brother,
I must ask for your help.
I will do as Sect Leader says.
However,
if I recruit Wang Lin to our cause,
I hope Senior Brother will reconsider
who is the best successor for Sect Leader.
Wen
Kuang
Eternal Night
never fades !
I truly don't know where Eternal Night Devil City is !
Eternal Night disciples
rarely venture outside !
In the entire Sea of Devils,
only one person knows its location.
The Xuanyu City Lord,
Lord Yu Yin.
Lord Yu Yin
resides in Xuanyu City.
Under soul-searching spells,
no one can lie.
I asked many people
and the information is consistent...
Why does no one know Eternal Night Devil City's location ?
There must be a reason...
But Wan'er's condition won't wait.
We must go to
this Xuanyu City.
Do you know Xuanyu City ?
I have heard about it,
it's said that Xuanyu City
is a bit strange.
Most residents are Nascent Soul cultivators.
And all who enter the city,
submit within days
to become subjects
willing to die for Lord Yu Yin.
It's indeed weird.
Since we know where
Xuanyu City is,
it might hold clues
about the Eternal Night Devil City.
Wan'er,
how do you feel ?
Thanks to Senior suppressing the poison,
I feel much better
Let me check.
As long as you don't cultivate,
the poison won't spread.
Xuanyu City is our only lead for now,
I must investigate it.
But I'm worried about leaving you alone.
I want to be with Senior.
No matter what we do,
Wan'er is willing.
Then let's go together.
This big bug
flies with such style !
Uncle Yu Yin,
you needn't trouble yourself
with Junior's affairs.
Yu Yin
Xuanyu City Lord
Middle stage Soul Formation
Senior Brother forbade your involvement.
And you are to return to Eternal Night Devil City.
But Wang Lin...
Leave him to Uncle.
How can your Uncle
not help
cleaning little Wen Kuang's mess...
But you don't need to rush back to Eternal Night Devil City.
If you return now
wouldn't it be shameful ?
You're making fun of me ?
Master,
have you lost faith in me ?
Master, I've reached Foundation Establishment !
Too slow...
Even with your talent,
you may not deserve to become the City Lord.
Ponder on this question.
How do you divine the outcome of a battle
with an unknown enemy ?
Your own fate is most accurate when doing divination,
so I would read my own fate.
Don't let me down.
As long as I can kill Wang Lin,
I can realize Eternal Night's grand plan.
And Master
will truly acknowledge me !
Xuanyu City
Inner Sea of Devils
Master and mistress are like a celestial couple !
How enviable !
Xu Liguo
A competitor in flattery ?!
At this rate,
my position as the number one subordinate
will be lost !
Shoo !
This is also something you can envy.
Master and mistress rode the Mosquito Beast
to travel through the Sea of Devils again.
Time really flies by !
They are destined to grow old together !
I'm Master's first disciple !
Get away from me !
Most residents are indeed Nascent Soul cultivators.
But the atmosphere here
is unexpectedly carefree.
So lively !
I've never seen such a prosperous city !
This is nothing like the reputation
of the Sea of Devils.
Here,
take it !
Quick, grab it !
Give it to me !
I've never seen cultivators laugh like this.
They seem so happy !
To build such a city in the Sea of Devils,
Yu Yin is truly extraordinary.
We must find him quickly...
Joy...
Disciple recognizes her,
she's a Heavenly Devil Palace Elder.
Heavenly Devil Palace Elder
Late stage Nascent Soul
Late stage Nascent Soul.
She's an arrogant cultivator...
I'll notify you when stock arrives
so you can buy one for your cultivation partner.
I'll look into this !
Safe travels !
Senior,
why are you selling goods here ?
You used to be at the Heavenly Devil Palace.
You were respected there
and had countless servants.
You must have mistaken me for someone else.
I...
Come take a look !
Fellow cultivator,
remember to visit our Tianyun Pavilion if you need !
This is a beast taming formation,
it absorbs spiritual energy to operate.
Marvelous,
truly marvelous !
Young lady is knowledgeable !
This formation was designed by the City Lord himself.
The City Lord is that powerful ?
Of course !
The City Lord is everyone's idol.
Each of his appearances
draws a huge crowd of admirers.
If only...
If only I were younger,
I'd join them too.
Senior,
I want to go to the City Lord's palace.
Do you know the way ?
You...
remembered something ?
This...
isn't the Heavenly Devil Palace !
How can her consciousness
be in such a state ?
Young lady is knowledgeable !
This lantern
is yours.
Thank you shopkeeper,
but I don't need it.
Young lady,
don't leave like that !
My lanterns are good quality,
every single one...
Noisy.
Please come again !
Mistress really is clever !
Yu Yin controls people with illusions.
Our probing alerted him
so we might not need to look for him
because he'll come to us himself.
Jewelry
and trinkets.
Come take a look fellow cultivator !
So it has begun.
In Xuanyu City,
death is the best outcome.
Even Master avoids this city like the plague.
Wang Lin...
You'll become a stepping stone for my Eternal Night Devil City !
Senior !
Give me your hand.
This is...
Senior,
I know cultivation is important
so we can't always be together.
I know that when you are alone,
it must feel lonely.
Can I be the star while your are the moon,
so that we can shine together night after night ?
Wan'er...
Wan'er,
wake up !
Senior...
What's going on ?
I...
This city is dangerous,
you were bewitched by it.
Yu Yin, come out !
Yu Yin,
since you know I'm here,
why are you fooling around ?
I can't let you take anymore risks with me.
Wan'er !
Senior,
this place amplifies our desires.
A single emotion,
a single thought,
will be magnified infinitely.
Indeed,
I was affected too
but missed the signs.
Wan'er...
Do you like it ?
Six Desires Domain
My lord !
City Lord !
Please favor me !
My lord !
Embrace your desires,
join me in
this city of ecstasy.
Mere tricks.
Hand over the location of Eternal Night Devil City !
Yu Yin manipulates desires
not via spells
but with his domain.
I've never seen such a domain...
He silently controls
the whole city.
I can't let Wan'er take anymore risks.
The Restriction Flag will block Yu Yin's domain,
stay here.
If you're in danger,
I'll return instantly.
Senior,
please be careful.
He's coming !
He's coming...
Master...
He's here !
Welcome to
Xuanyu City,
the warmest place in your life.
My first Soul Formation puppet,
nice to meet you.
You're just all talk !
Your desire domain is hard to detect
but I've experienced it before
with the Six Desires Devil Lord.
The Devil Lord ?
He was my Junior Brother.
But his spells
were just pale imitations
of my Six Desires.
He can't compare to me.
Under the law of the heavens,
desires are lowly.
Life and Death Domain...
Activate !
Life and Death Domain
Domains stems from the mental state
and after your time in this city,
your mind has been eroded
and your desires are unstable.
Where is your domain ?
A strong domain
is useless
if you can't use it !
I've been Soul Formation for a thousand years.
The Six Desires Domain invades the mind
and countless desires nourish it.
This Xuanyu City
is my millennia of cultivation !
Hatred !
Kill him !
Look at what I have prepared for you.
Anger !
Life is but a fleeting dream,
a bitter struggle for survival,
an endless path of cultivation.
But in the end,
all we seek
is joy,
anger,
sorrow,
fear,
love
and hatred.
Why don't you
surrender yourself to me
to spare yourself the suffering of pursuing desires
and to taste the most extreme desires directly ?
Wouldn’t that be better ?
Senior !
The mental attacks are growing stronger each time.
If he stirs enough of my desires,
I'll fall into his illusion
and be controlled.
Nascent Souls,
no matter how many of of you there are,
I’ll crush you all !
Thanks for the hospitality.
Now have a taste
of my own collection !
Dreamweaving !
Interesting...
How interesting !
Go !
Watch out above !
Devour !
2 desires remain...
Come on !
Let's take our time.
Look,
who is that ?
Senior !
Wan’er !
Fear.
How dare you ?!
Senior !
Too late...
What a pity...
Sorrow.
Wan’er...
He did it !
I can’t break the Restriction Flag guarding that woman.
But illusions blending reality
are impossible for you to defend against.
It's a pity that the Lord of Eternal Night is so powerful,
I couldn’t even detect a trace of his desires.
So I couldn’t turn him into a puppet...
But you, Wang Lin,
will do just fine.
Uncle, you’re amazing !
How did you control him ?
Within my domain
Core Formation and Nascent Soul cultivators
need only 1 or 2 desires ignited
in order to bend to my will.
Soul Formation cultivators are trickier
I ignited 4 desires
to deceive him with illusions.
And I ignited all 6
to make him a puppet
that will do as I please.
Congratulations Uncle,
for your new Soul Formation puppet.
You already have a strand of my Divine Sense.
I used this bracelet as a link
to reinforce the connection.
Xuanyu City is strange
so I may be victim of illusions.
That's where you come in.
Senior...
Wan’er is here !
Senior, open your eyes !
Don’t worry, Senior.
Senior, be careful !
Senior !
Wake up !
Senior...
Wan’er...
Senior !
Wake up quickly !
Senior...
I wish you could stay with me forever.
But
you must wake up now.
Impossible...
You can’t break free from the Six Desires Domain !
Your Six Desires Domain
is just a mere trick
played by your cowardly self.
In a real domain battle,
it’s utterly worthless...
Break !
No one...
No one can defy me !
I am the Lord of Xuanyu City !
You used Wan’er to deceive me.
You...
deserve death !
Yu Yin !
This...
How is this possible ?!
Wan’er !
Wan’er...
Senior...
I...
What happened ?
Where is my hand !?
What happened !?
Yan’er !
I was just at the Heavenly Devil Palace...
Who is the one
who brought me here !?
I...
Why am I so old ?!
What year is it ?!
Wang Lin...
I’ve sealed the poisoned blood.
I set up a restriction
so you can rest safely.
Thank you Senior.
I can't keep suppressing the poison,
we must go to Eternal Night Devil City.
Who are you !?
You should have guessed.
His first move always counters my follow-up...
It's as if I'm actively delivering attacks for him to block.
The Thunder Toad's attacks rival Middle stage Soul Formation
but if they can't hit,
they're useless.
You found the cave hidden by my ancient restriction
and predicted all of my attacks.
You're worthy of the title of Lord of Eternal Night.
But if you truly have an omniscient domain,
I don't think the law of the heavens would tolerate it.
Wrong.
My omniscience
is but part of the law of the heavens.
Just hand over the antidote and Wen Kuang.
I have no ill will toward Eternal Night Devil City.
I know you won't spare Wen Kuang.
And I don't have another 500 years
to raise another successor.
The antidote is in my bag of holding.
Let's settle this with a fight to the death !
I can't match a Late stage Soul Formation.
He knows all my artifacts and spells
as well as everything I will do.
My only advantage lies in my domain.
Life and Death Domain...
Activate !
I reached Soul Formation
Calculation Domain
with
the Calculation Domain.
Die !
Original body !
Wang Lin's original body
2-stars Ancient God
Wang Lin
Early stage Soul Formation
and 2-stars Ancient God
As expected,
your fate
is already set.
Young Master,
the Lord has ordered
you to go to the Ancestral Hall.
Wen Kuang,
when you hear this
My Soul Blood jade !
it means that I'm fighting Wang Lin
and I that will die very soon.
The strength of Ancient Gods defies all logic.
The rise of our Eternal Night Devil City has been arduous.
For 6 000 years,
we never gave up on the dream of becoming a rank 5 country.
I calculated the rise of Eternal Night Devil City.
And I also calculated a calamity.
It was just 5 days ago
that I realized
that this calamity
is Wang Lin.
Both of your bodies
shall die with me.
I've calculated the outcome of countless battles with Wang Lin
but all of them lead to my death.
But only through my death
will the sole path for our survival appear.
That path is you.
This is our inescapable fate.
Fate ?!
Remember,
when doing divination,
one misstep
can lead to eternal damnation.
All these years,
the calamity weighed on me like a boulder.
I desperately hoped you'd be ready before it.
Child,
I hope you can fulfill
my 6 000 years of ambition.
Master !
Eternal Night
never fades !
His artifacts
are gone ?
Something's wrong.
With the power of the Lord of Eternal Night,
how could he not know of my second body ?
Wan'er,
wait for me.
Rain is filling the sky,
hanging off a thousand years of destiny.
This blossoming flower of love
reflects my eternal devotion to you.
Under the starlight,
in my broken dreams,
my memories are stained by the passage of time.
I must find a sentence I won't regret
and a life without fear.
The brushstrokes of red dust
sketches out the law of cause and effect.
You're finally cured.
I was hooked after a single glance,
an intense heat is burning in my palm.
I will refine myself day and night,
I will devote my entire life to you.
Your appearance
is engraved in my dreams.
We will be reborn together.
Fate has changed but our journey continues.
We've been through many things
so believe in me, not in fate.
Senior...
Take me on your endless journey
of awakening through slaughter.
I will break through those illusions with you.
Together, we will walk across the rainbows.
That's...
Soul Formation ?
Someone is reaching Soul Formation ?
Wen Kuang
New Lord of Eternal Night
Late stage Soul Formation
That's...
Envoy !
No,
the City Lord !
He just broke through
but his cultivation directly reached Late stage Soul Formation !
The heavens bless our Eternal Night Devil City !
Welcome City Lord !
All Eternal Night Devil City members
will help to activate
the Ten Thousand Souls Fate-Altering Formation !
All the 84 000 calculations
point to the same dead end.
Note: a life palace is a metaphysical term used in divination and chinese astrology
From his life palace to the problem of his Lingtai acupuncture point,
I know everything about him !
Ten Thousand Souls
Fate-Altering Formation
I am sure
he will die in this battle !
Wan'er !
Li Muwan's
Sea of Consciousness
Senior...
My soul seems to be getting extracted.
The disciples who died from the poison in our sect
all lost their souls.
A Soul Extracting spell...
The poison was just a decoy for soul extraction.
Don't worry,
our souls are already connected.
I'll reinforce the bond for now.
Your soul won't be lost.
I will definitely bring you back.
Senior,
be careful...
Eternal Night Devil City...
Wang Lin,
I've been waiting for you.
Where is Wan'er ?
Do you want to know ?
Wang Lin,
you brought this upon yourself !
The person before you
is Wen Kuang.
And also my Master.
And all the previous Lords of Eternal Night !
Beneath your feet
lies a 6 000 years old formation.
All previous Lords of Eternal Night
used it before their death
to let their successors alter their own fate
by inheriting everything.
Memories,
cultivation,
and artifacts
have been passed down through generations.
Master's Calculation Domain
improved the formation.
Making it
no longer require Soul Blood
but by using a soul connection instead.
This explains what happened with the Lord of Eternal Night.
But where is Wan'er ?
Master calculated you'd connect your soul with Li Muwan
in your battle against Yu Yin.
He used his death to decieve you
and to make you discover that Li Muwan's soul was getting extracted
so that you would reinforce your soul connection again.
You dare to use Wan'er
as a Formation core !?
Master calculated that his death
would be the final piece to complete
the Ten Thousand Souls Fate-Altering Formation.
How could it be ?
To make me
usurp your fate !
This is Master's
great plan.
Restriction Spear
Devour !
My Fate Domain combined with the formation
use ten thousand souls as fuel
to delve into the river of fate
and transfer your destiny to me.
Everything you possess
will become mine !
He became a Soul Devourer !?
You
will become the stepping stone that will make Eternal Night Devil City
a rank 5 country !
Wang Lin,
I'll make you watch as I take everything from you,
piece by piece,
until you have nothing left
and beg on you knees
for death.
He has calculated everything about me...
In that case,
I only have one move left.
These carvings
are mine now.
Wan'er !
Wan'er is linking me to the formation core.
The one thing he can't usurp
is my past with Wan'er.
Now that our fates are linked,
taking your power will be effortless.
So what if you stole my fate ?
So you need to see it to believe it.
This
is the Ji Realm !
You are so impatient.
Wang Lin,
do you know how many domains
my Ancestors have mastered
in 6 000 years ?
The Lost Domain.
Lost Domain
Ocean Domain
The Ocean Domain.
The Wrath Domain.
Wrath Domain
Enough !
You've finally unleashed your domain.
Wang Lin,
have you ever tasted
your own domain ?
Formation shift.
Truly worth the title of Ancient God.
Usurping it,
took considerable time.
Your Ancient God body
is now mine !
You have nothing left
but broken bones
and a shattered Origin Soul.
You would be better off dead.
Now
is the moment to destroy the formation's core !
Wen Kuang's
Sea of Counsciousness
Wan'er !
Senior, be careful !
Wang Lin...
You have calculated everything
except the War God Shrine's Divine Path
which is beyond your comprehension.
So you didn't know
that both my bodies have a Divine Sense.
My original body and I
share our existence through the Divine Path.
We are one and the same.
You stole my Ancient God body
and now its Divine Sense has invaded your Sea of Counsiousness.
Formation,
activate !
You've lost your Ancient God body,
so what if you can still use your Divine Sense ?
I just need more time to refine it.
Senior,
these hexagrams are the formation's core.
Destroy 4 of them and it will shatter.
You speak,
I attack.
The rules keep changing.
Trigram of Kun,
southwest !
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Trigram of Kan,
north !
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
Northwest !
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down !
I look towards the top.
Enough !
Chase !
Fate-Altering Formation !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Don't look back
Be careful Senior  !
at our unfinished vows.
Don't be afraid of this dangerous path,
even if it's just for a second.
This fog cannot be blown away.
Wan'er !
Through the stormy night
the peaks and throughs overlap.
At this point
Every moment,
I will personally destroy this formation's core !
we share our destiny.
The outcome of our journey is set in stone
Let's
but even predetermined endings can be changed.
die together !
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
The 6 000 years of rise of Eternal Night Devil City
can't be ruined by you !
Even the sharpest thorns
I don't care about
the rise of your damn city !
will be reduced into ashes.
I refuse to accept this !
What is there to fear ?
Senior !
No...
No !
The Divine Path...
The Divine Path technique...
In my entire life,
this was my only mistake !
6 000 years of waiting
just to be one step short !
Just one step...
Just one step !
Eternal Night
never fades...
never...
Die !
fades...
Southern Courtyard
Cloud Sky Sect
Wan'er,
failing to form a Nascent Soul
is no reason to lose heart.
Remember what I taught you,
use the artifacts I gave you,
and the pills of the Cloud Sky Sect.
I asked the palm lines of time,
Senior,
Wan'er promises
that she will succeed next time.
sincerely entrust your love, don't waste time.
Senior,
you can leave with peace of mind.
I promised in my dreams
I'll return as soon as possible.
that from now on no one will block our path.
Senior doesn't need to worry.
Although the path of cultivation is long,
In the blink of an eye, I will change the world.
Wan'er will walk it with you.
But maybe not this morning.
In all these nights of longing for the past,
deep in my heart
I believed that you and I
can cross the line between life and death.
We will overcome our doomed fate.
The night won't last forever.
I believe that fate will never destroy our vows.
Thank you all for your support of Renegade Immortal.
Rain is filling the sky,
hanging off a thousand years of destiny.
This blossoming flower of love
reflects my eternal devotion to you.
Under the starlight,
in my broken dreams,
my memories are stained by the passage of time.
I must find a sentence I won't regret
and a life without fear.
The brushstrokes of red dust
sketches out the law of cause and effect.
I was hooked after a single glance,
an intense heat is burning in my palm.
I will refine myself day and night,
I will devote my entire life to you.
Your appearance
is engraved in my dreams.
I defy heaven and earth
because my immortal body exists only to embrace you.
I will reverse the cycle of reincarnation
so I can can see your reflection in the sky.
I defy the darkness and loneliness.
You are the one by my side as I ascend to immortality.
I defy the wind, the flowers and the moon.
I will live on forever.
I tread on the sky to imitate
how I tread on the fate that pulls us apart.
The passing of time
cannot wear down my indomitable spirit.
I don't fear death for you,
for love knows no bounds even when our dreams fade.
This boundless and endless love
will be with you forever.
We will be reborn together.
Fate has changed but our journey continues.
We've been through many things
so believe in me, not in fate.
Take me on your endless journey
of awakening through slaughter.
I will break through those illusions with you.
Together, we will walk across the rainbows.
We will be reborn together.
Fate has changed but our journey continues.
We've been through many things
so believe in me, not in fate.
Take me on your endless journey
of awakening through slaughter.
I will break through those illusions with you.
Together, we will walk across the rainbows.
Law of the heavens,
this time
you will not take her from me !